filecloud.com 2005-12-12

# Filecloud - Privacy

* Filecloud is committed to respecting your privacy. Once you choose to provide personally identifiable information, it will only be used in the context of your customer relationship with Filecloud. 

* On various Filecloud web pages you can order services, make requests, and register to receive materials or support. The types of personal information collected at these pages are name, username, contact and billing information, transaction, and credit card information. Data collected online may also be combined with information provided during ownership registration of Filecloud products and services. In order to tailor subsequent communications and continuously improve products and services, Filecloud may ask you to voluntarily provide information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, product experience, and contact information. 

* Filecloud will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to others. Unless required by law, Filecloud will only share the personal data provided with business partners who are acting on our behalf to complete the activities you requested. Such business partners are governed by Filecloud's privacy policy with respect to the use of this data. Unless required by law, should a company not governed by Filecloud's privacy policy require your personal information, your permission will be initially obtained. If you choose to share such information, the use of that data will be governed by the company's respective privacy policy. 

* Filecloud uses your information to better understand customer needs and continuously improve the level of service provided. Specifically, your information is used to help complete a transaction, to communicate back to you, to update you on service and benefits, and to personalize Filecloud's web site. Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not utilized for other purposes. 

* From time to time, Filecloud may use your information to contact you for market research or to provide you with information thought to be of particular interest. At a minimum, you have the opportunity to opt out of receiving such direct marketing or market research contact. Where applicable, Filecloud will also follow local requirements such as allowing you to opt in before receiving an unsolicited contact. 

* Filecloud strives to keep your personally identifiable information accurate. Every effort is made to provide you with online access to your registration data so that you may update or correct your information at any time. Filecloud is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, appropriate procedures are in place to safeguard and secure the information collected online. Filecloud uses encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. 

* Filecloud is a [Speakeasy Broadband Services](http://www.speakeasy.net/), LLC Property
